[
 {
   "No": 1,
   "Quiz question": "Which actor is the lead singer of a famous American band “30 Seconds to Mars”?",
   "Answer": "Jared Leto"
 },
 {
   "No": 2,
   "Quiz question": "Which actor played the role of a Russian boxer, Ivan Drago, in “Rocky 4”?",
   "Answer": "Dolph Lundgren"
 },
 {
   "No": 3,
   "Quiz question": "Which actor is well-known for his roles in “The Hurt Locker”, “The Bourne Legacy”, “American Hustle”.",
   "Answer": "Jeremy Renner"
 },
 {
   "No": 4,
   "Quiz question": "Which actor appeared in famous films, such as “Gone in 60 Seconds”, “Face/Off”, “Ghost Rider”.",
   "Answer": "Nicholas Cage"
 },
 {
   "No": 5,
   "Quiz question": "Which actor was cast in “Kingpin” - a famous 90’s comedy.",
   "Answer": "Woody Harrelson"
 },
 {
   "No": 6,
   "Quiz question": "Which actor played James Bond in 1990?",
   "Answer": "Pierce Brosnan"
 },
 {
   "No": 7,
   "Quiz question": "Which actor used to be a professional football player?",
   "Answer": "Vinnie Jones"
 },
 {
   "No": 8,
   "Quiz question": "Which actor played the role of a famous fictional serial killer - Hannibal Lecter?",
   "Answer": "Anthony Hopkins"
 },
 {
   "No": 9,
   "Quiz question": "Which actor played the role of the most famous contemporary vampire?",
   "Answer": "Robert Pattinson"
 },
 {
   "No": 10,
   "Quiz question": "Name a famous actor with 3 Oscars for the films “My Left Foot”, “There Will be Blood”, “Lincoln”.",
   "Answer": "Daniel Day-Lewis"
 },
 {
   "No": 11,
   "Quiz question": "Which actor played the famous hobbit - Frodo?",
   "Answer": "Elijah Wood"
 },
 {
   "No": 12,
   "Quiz question": "Who is the most famous Hemsworth brother?",
   "Answer": "Chris Hemsworth"
 },
 {
   "No": 13,
   "Quiz question": "Who played Wolverine?",
   "Answer": "Hugh Jackman"
 },
 {
   "No": 14,
   "Quiz question": "Despite his fame, he is often seen sad and completely alone on the streets.",
   "Answer": "Keanu Reeves"
 },
 {
   "No": 15,
   "Quiz question": "Which actor was awarded Oscars for the films “Glory” and “Training Day”?",
   "Answer": "Denzel Washington"
 },
 {
   "No": 16,
   "Quiz question": "What is the real name of Oprah Winfrey, a famous American TV host?",
   "Answer": "Orpah"
 },
 {
   "No": 17,
   "Quiz question": "Marilyn Manson’s real first name?",
   "Answer": "Bryan"
 },
 {
   "No": 18,
   "Quiz question": "Actor Jerry Springer, famous for his roles in “Sunset Beach” and “Four funerals and a wedding”, was the mayor of which town?",
   "Answer": "Cincinnati, Ohio"
 },
 {
   "No": 19,
   "Quiz question": "Which coffee chain did Madonna work at?",
   "Answer": "Dunkin Donuts"
 },
 {
   "No": 20,
   "Quiz question": "Which actor traveled with the circus at the age of 15 and was a tamer?",
   "Answer": "Chuck Norris"
 }
]
